longdom.org 2019-05-03

# Longdom Publishing | Privacy Policy

Longdom Publishing is committed to respecting the privacy of the personal information we collect from you. This privacy policy sets forth our practices regarding collection, use and disclosure of information collected through all Longdom Publishing websites (each a “Site”). Note that we reserve the right to change this policy at any time without notice. Any changes will be posted on this page. The Sites of Longdom Publishing group may have different privacy policies. In such cases, the privacy policy of that Site will supersede the terms of this policy. This Site may contain links to other websites that are beyond our control. This privacy policy will not apply to data collected by these websites.

Collection of Personal Information

The information collected directly from a user may include contact information, such as the user’s name, email address, and postal address. This personal information can be used for delivering our products or services, processing orders, or responding to your inquiries, researching and developing new products and services, and/or communicating with you about changes to our products and services,or about special offers.

We may retain your personal information for as long as it is relevant to our business purposes or until you request that we remove it.

We endeavor to keep your personal information confidential and protected against unauthorized access, loss, misuse or alteration through the use of appropriate administrative, physical and technical safeguards. The information about each user is stored on systems that are subject to appropriate security measures, and we limit employee access to such information.

Disclosure of Personal Information

Access to your personal information is restricted to our employees, service providers, and entities for which we are acting as an agent, licensee or publisher. Your personal information may be transferred to other countries for processing. These countries may not have similar data privacy laws. Note that we will not disclose any personal information without your consent except under the following circumstances:

  * in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our rights to defend against legal claims;
  * to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, safety of person or property, violation of our policies, or as otherwise required by law;
  * if Longdom Publishing, this Site, or a related asset or line of business is acquired by, transferred to or merged with another company.

In addition, we may contract with third-party advertisers or service providers that post on the Site banner advertisements, which may link to other websites not under our control, or that use technologies to collect and process user data. Use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies, which may differ from this privacy policy. We are not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products or other materials offered from such third parties.

Questions and Dispute Resolution

If you have any questions or complaints regarding the way your personal information is being handled, please contact Longdom Publishing’s Data Protection Office at:  
Avenue Roger Vandendriessche,  
18, 1150 Brussels, Belgium  
Email: [info@longdom.org](mailto:info@longdom.org)

The Longdom Publishing Data Protection Office will make reasonable efforts to promptly investigate and, if necessary, to correct any problem.
